（伯克斯威尔 一年前）
在你们离开之前
And before you leave.
这个苹果派 免费赠送
One of our apple pies. On the house.
天啊 太感谢了
Oh, my God, thank you so much.
- 不用谢 - 我们应该多迷几次路
- You're welcome. - Hey, we should get lost more often.
我是说这镇子上的人太善良了
I mean, everyone in this town is so nice.
是的 看看你手上拿的
Yeah, what's the catch?
- 全都准备好了 - 谢谢
- You're all set. - Thanks.
纹身很酷
That's a cool tattoo.
谢谢
Thanks.
现在给你指条上州际公路的路
So let's get you back to the interstate.
麻烦你了
Yeah, please.
从这小路直接出镇子
Take Lasky straight out of town.
然后在果园小路右转
And then turn right on Orchard Road.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thank you.
怎么了？
What happened?
不知道
I don't know.
车子挂掉了
Car just died.
手机也是
Cell phone too.
怎么可能？
How's that possible?
过来吧 那边好象有房子
Come on. Looks like a house over there.
不 我才不过去
No, I'm not going in there.
亲爱的 我们需要帮助
Holly, we need help.
不能一直等在这里
We can't just wait here.
好吧
Come on. Okay.
看看吧
Check it out.
「如果我们有大脑」
lf I only had a brain.
我们就不会迷路 谢谢
We wouldn't be lost. Thanks.
这是我见过最他妈畸形的稻草人
That has got to be the freakiest damn scarecrow I've ever seen.
吓着我了
It scares me.
拜托 快点离开 好吗？
Please, let's just hurry, okay?
你听见了？
Did you hear that?
喂 谁在哪儿？
Hello? Who's there?
文森
Vince?
《邪恶力量》
迪恩。-
Dean.
喂 萨姆 是你吗？
Hello? Sam, is that you?
爸爸 你受伤了吗？
Dad. Are you hurt?
我没事
l'm fine.
我们到处找你
We've been looking for you everywhere.
不知道你在哪儿
We didn't know where you were.
也不知道你是否还好
If you were okay.
萨姆 我很好
Sammy, l'm all right.
你和迪恩呢？
What about you and Dean?
我们都还好
We're fine.
爸爸 你在哪儿
Dad, where are you?
抱歉孩子 我还不能告诉你
Sorry, kiddo, I can't tell you that.
什么？
What?
为什么不能？
Why not?
是爸爸吗？
ls that Dad?
听着 我知道你很难理解
Look, I know this is hard for you to understand. You just.
你只要相信我
You're gonna have to trust me on this.
你在追踪它 是吗？
You're after it, aren't you?
杀害妈妈的凶手
The thing that killed Mom?
是的 是个恶魔 萨姆
Yeah. It's a demon, Sam.
恶魔？
A demon?
你确定？
You know for sure?
恶魔？
A demon?
他说什么？
What's he saying?
我确定
I do.
听着 萨姆
Listen, Sammy, l, uh…
我也知道发生在你女朋友身上的事
I also know what happened to your girlfriend.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我已经尽力让你躲避它了
I would've done anything to protect you from that.
你知道它在哪儿？
You know where it is?
是的 我已经最终接近它了
Yeah, I think I'm finally closing in on him.
让我们来帮忙
Let us help.
你们不能
You can't.
你们不能参与进来
You can't be any part of it.
为什么
Why not?
把电话给我
Give me the phone.
听着 萨姆 这就是我打电话来的原因
Listen, Sammy, that's why l'm calling.
你和你哥哥得停止找我
You and your brother, you gotta stop looking for me.
我要你记下这些名字
Now, I need you to write down these names.
名字？
Names?
什么名字 爸爸
What names?Dad, why?
跟我说
Talk to me.
告诉我这到底是怎么回事
Tell me what's going on.
我们没时间讨论这个了
Look, we don't have time for this.
这比你想的要麻烦得很多 它们无处不在
This is bigger than you think. They're everywhere.
就算是现在我们现在说话
Even us talking right now.
也不安全
It's not safe.
不行
No, all right?
绝对不行
No way.
把电话给我
Give me the phone!
现在我命令你
I've given you an order.
停止找我
Now, you stop following me.
做你该做的
And you do your job.
明白吗？
You understand me?
现在记下这些名字
Now, take down these names.
爸爸 是我 你在哪儿？
Dad, it's me. Where are you?
明白
Yes, sir.
是的 我拿到笔了
Yeah, I got a pen.
什么名字？
What are the names?
好了 爸爸给的这些名字
All right, so the names Dad gave us.
全是夫妇的？
They're all couples?
三对不同的夫妇都失踪了
Three different couples, all went missing.
他们在不同的州不同的小镇上失踪的？
From different towns, different states?
是的 华盛顿 纽约 科罗拉多
That's right, yeah. Washington, New York, Colorado.
每对夫妇都是在乡村公路旅行
Each couple took a road trip cross-country.
没有一对是到达目的地的
None arrived at their destination.
也再没有他们的消息
or were ever heard from again.
乡村是很大的 迪恩
It's a big country.
他们可能在任何地方失踪
They could've disappeared anywhere.
是的 有可能
Could've.
但是所有的路线都把他们送到印地安那的同一个地方
But each one's route took them through the same part of Indiana.
而且都是在四月的第二个星期
Always on the second week of April.
一年接一年再接一年
One year after another after another.
现在就是四月的第二个星期
This is the second week of April.
正解 所以爸爸就叫我们去印地安那
Yep.So Dad is sending us to lndiana…
在下一对夫妇消失之前把那家伙给干掉
to go hunting for something before another couple vanishes?
猜对了
Yahtzee.
你能想象一下把这些全部整理起来吗？
Can you imagine putting together a pattern like this?
爸爸参加了所有这些葬礼
The different obits Dad had to go through?
他是牧师
The man's a master.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
我们不去印地安那
We're not going to Indiana.
不去？
We're not?
不去 我们要加利福尼亚
No, we're going to California.
爸爸是从公用电话打来的
Dad called from a pay phone.
是萨克拉曼多的区号 （加州首府）
With a Sacramento area code.
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩 如果爸爸现在接近的是 杀死妈妈和杰西的凶手
Dean, if this demon killed Mom and Jess, and Dad's closing in.
我们就该去
We gotta be there.
我们该去帮爸爸
We gotta help.
爸爸不需要我们的帮助
Dad doesn't want our help.
我不管
Well, I don't care.
他给我们下达了命令
He has given us an order.
我不管
I don't care.
我们不要总是对他惟命是从
We don't always have to do what he says.
萨姆 爸爸叫我们做本职工作
Sam, Dad is asking us to work jobs.
拯救生命 那才是最重要的
to save lives. It's important.
好吧 我能理解 相信我 我能理解
All right, I understand. Believe me.
但是我只是说耽误一个星期 伙计
But l'm talking one week here, man.
找到答案
To get answers.
然后报仇
To get revenge.
听着 我明白你的感受
All right, look, I know how you feel.
你明白？
Do you?
妈妈死的时候你多大
How old were you when Mom died?
四岁？
Four?
六个星期前杰西才去世
Jess died six months ago.
你怎么可能明白我的感受？
How the hell would you know how I feel?
爸爸说那对我们来说太危险
Dad said it wasn't safe for any of us.
就算他知道些我们不知道的事情
He obviously knows something that we don't.
他叫我们靠边站 我们就得靠边站
If he says stay away, we stay away.
我实在不能理解你对他的盲目崇拜
I don't understand the blind faith you have in the man.
你甚至对他没有任何疑问
I mean, it's like you don't even question him.
至少这叫做孝顺的孩子
Yeah, it's called being a good son.
你是个自私的杂种
You're a selfish bastard.
知道吗？
You know that?
你总是任性妄为
You just do whatever you want.
根本不在乎其他人怎么想
Don't care what anybody thinks.
你真的是这么认为的？
That's what you really think?
当然
Yes, it is.
好吧 自私的杂种要去加利福尼亚了
Well, then this selfish bastard is going to California.
- 够了 你不是认真的吧 - 我手是认真的
- Come on, you're not serious. - I am serious.
现在是半夜
It's the middle of the night.
嘿 我要走了
Hey, I'm taking off.
我要把你扔在这里 听见了吗？
I will leave your ass, you hear me?
我就想你这么干
That's what I want you to do.
那再见吧 萨姆
Goodbye, Sam.
让我猜猜 Scotty？
Let me guess. Scotty.
是的
Yep.
我叫约翰·巴纳姆
Hi, my name's John Bonham.
齐柏林飞船鼓手？
Isn't that the drummer for Led Zeppelin?
不错
Wow. Good.
摇滚狂热者
Classic rock fan.
我能帮你做点什么吗 约翰
What can I do for you, John?
我想知道你是否可能见过这些人
Was wondering if, uh, you've seen these people, by chance.
没有 他们是谁
Nope. Who are they?
我的朋友
Friends of mine.
他们大约一年前失踪
They went missing about a year ago.
他们好象路过这附近
They passed through somewhere here.
我已经去过斯科特斯勃格和塞伦了
I asked around Scottsburg and Salem.
抱歉 这里不常有外地人
Sorry. We don't get many strangers around here.
斯科蒂 如果你笑一笑就会照亮整个屋子
Scotty, you got a smile that lights up a room.
有人告诉过你吗？
Anybody ever tell you that?
别介意
Never mind.
待会儿见
See you around.
嗨
Hey.
你把我吓死了
You scared the hell out of me.
抱歉 我只是想你是否需要帮助
I'm sorry. I just thought you might need some help.
我很好 谢谢
Um, I'm good, thanks.
去哪儿？
Uh, so where you headed?
无意冒犯 但是我不想告诉你
No offense, but no way l'm telling you.
为什么
Why not?
你可能是个精神病
You could be some kind of freak.
我的意思你是个搭便车的
l mean, you are hitchhiking.
你也是啊
Well, so are you.
要搭车吗？
Need a ride?
- 是的 - 是的 只带她
- Yeah, yeah. - Yeah. Just her.
我不会带你
I aingt taking you.
你相信一个可疑的货车男也不相信我？
You trust shady van guy and not me?
那是当然
Definitely.
你确定他们没有停下来加油或其他什么？
You sure they didn't stop for gas or something?
没有 不记得有他们
Nope, don't remember them.
你说他们是你的朋友？
You say they were friends of yours?
- 没错 - 那人身上有纹身吗？
- That's right. - Did the guy have a tattoo?
是的 有
Yes, he did.
还记得吗？
You remember?
他们才刚刚结婚
They were just married.
你是对的 他们来加过油
You're right. They did stop for gas.
停留不超过10分钟
Weren't here more than 1 0 minutes.
你还记得什么？
Do you remember anything else?
我告诉他们怎么回州际公路
Told them how to get to the interstate.
然后他们就离开镇子了
They left town.
你能给我指一下路吗？
Could you point me in that direction?
当然
Sure.
见鬼
What the hell?
伙计 你可真郁闷
Dude, you fugly.
干得好
Nice tat.
你又回来了
You're back.
根本就没走
Never left.
还在找你的朋友？
You still looking for your friends?
不介意帮我装满好吗 艾米丽
Mind filling it up there, Emily?
你在这里长大的？
So did you grow up here?
我13岁的时候到这里
Came here when I was 1 3.
我失去了父母
I lost my parents.
车祸
A car accident.
我姑妈和伯父抚养我长大
My aunt and uncle took me in.
真是善良的人
They're nice people.
这里每个人都很善良
Everybody's nice here.
那这个小镇就很完美了？
So, what, it's the, uh, perfect little town?
虽然远离市区 但我喜欢这里
Well, you know, it's the boonies, but I love it.
我们周围的那些镇子
I mean, the towns around us…
人们失去房子 农场
people are losing their homes, their farms.
但是这里
But here.
就像受到祝福一样
It's almost like we're blessed.
你去过郊外的果园吗
Hey, you been out to the orchard?
见过那个稻草人？
Seen that That scarecrow?
是的 把我吓跑了
Yeah, it creeps me out.
- 那是谁的？- 不知道
- Whose is it? - I don't know.
一直都在那儿
It's just always been there.
那是你姑妈伯父的？
That your aunt and uncle's?
顾客的 车子有些小问题
Customer. Had some car troubles.
是两个人 是不是一男一女？
It's not a couple, is it? A guy and a girl?
抱歉 到萨克拉曼多的车明天才会来
Sorry, the Sacramento bus doesn't run again till tomorrow.
下午5 05
5:05 p.m.
明天？
Tomorrow?
应该还有其他办法
There's gotta be another way.
有啊 买辆车吧
Well, there is. Buy a car.
嗨
Hey.
又见到你了
You again.
你的顺风车怎么了？
What happened to your ride?
你是对的
You were right.
那家伙是很可疑
That guy was shady.
毛手毛脚的
Was all hands.
我把他甩掉了
I cut him loose.
怎么了
What's the matter?
想办法去加利福尼亚
Just trying to get to California.
不可能
No way.
是啊 我也是
Yeah. Me too.
下一班车要明天才来
You know, next bus isn't until tomorrow.
是的
Yeah. Yeah.
这就是麻烦所在
That's the problem.
为什么
Why?
加利福尼亚有什么东西这么重要
What's in Cali that's so important?
只是我一直在寻找的东西
Just something I've been looking for for a long time.
我肯定再等一天也没关系 对吧
Well, then l'm sure it can wait one more day, right?
我是梅格 萨姆
I'm Meg. Sam.
我们这里以苹果闻名
We're famous for our apples.
所以你们应该尝尝这馅饼
So you gotta try this pie.
不用了 谢谢
Oh, no, please.
没关系 免费赠送
Nope, it's on the house.
你好斯科蒂
Hiya, Scotty.
给我来杯咖啡好吗 黑咖啡
Can I get a coffee, black?
还来份那种馅饼
Oh, and some of that pie too, while you're at it.
你好 路过的？
How you doing? Just passing through?
公路旅行
Road trip. Mm.
我也是
Yeah, me too.
我想他们想安静的吃饭
I'm sure these people wanna eat in peace.
只是友好的交谈
Just a little friendly conversation.
我也要那咖啡
Oh, and that coffee too, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
你们怎么来到这镇子的？
So, what brings you to town?
停下来给车子加油
We just stopped for gas…
加油站的人救了我们的命
and, uh, the guy at the gas station saved our lives.
是这样的吗？
ls that right?
是的 车子的刹车油泄漏了
Yeah. One of our brake lines was leaking.
我们却没发现
We had no idea.
他正在帮我们修理
He's fixing it for us.
真是好人
Nice people.
- 是啊 - 你们什么时候上路？
- Yeah. - So how long until you up and running?
- 日落的时候 - 真的吗
- Sundown. - Really?
修理刹车
To fix a brake line?
嗯 我对修车也略知一二
You know, I know a thing or two about cars.
我可以免费为你们修车 让你们在一个小时之后就能上路
I could have you running in an hour. Wouldn't charge you.
十分感谢
You know, thanks a lot.
但是我更愿意让一个专业技工来做
But I think we'd rather have a mechanic do it.
当然
Sure, yeah.
你知道这段路
You know, it's just that these roads, um.
晚上不太安全
They're not real safe at night.
什么意思
I'm sorry?
我知道这听起来很奇怪
I know it sounds strange.
但是你们可能会很危险
But, uh, you might be in danger.
让我们好好吃饭 好吗？
We're trying to eat, okay?
好的
Yeah.
我弟弟一定会展示他那张纯洁幼稚的脸
You know, my brother could give you this puppy-dog look…
然后你们就会相信他
and you'd just buy right into it.
感谢你的到来 治安官
Thanks for coming, sheriff.
我想和你谈谈
Like a word, please.
够了 我今天已经够倒霉的了
Come on. I'm having a bad day already.
你肯定不想变得更倒霉
You don't want to make it worse.
你现在是在休假还是什么？
So, what, are you on some kind of vacation or something?
是的
Yeah, right.
就像是游泳池边散步一样
It's all sipping Cristal poolside for me.
不是这样的 我不得不
No. I had to…
离家出走
get away from my family.
为什么
Why?
我爱我的父母
I love my parents.
他们也想把最好的给我
And they wanted what's best for me.
但是他们并知道我想要的是什么
They just didn't care if I wanted it.
他们觉得我应该聪明一点
I was supposed to be smart.
但并不是聪明得吓跑了丈夫
But not smart enough to scare away a husband.
这只是… 因为我家人是这样说的
No. It's just…because my family said so…
我应该乖乖地坐着 做他吩咐我做的
l'm supposed to sit there and do what I was told.
所以我就离家出走
So I just went on my own way instead.
对不起 说了让你难以理解的话
m sorry. The things you say to people you hardly know.
不 我知道
No, no, it's okay.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
还记得之前我提到的哥哥？跟我一起旅行的
Remember that brother I mentioned before, that I was road tripping with?
跟你的情况类似
It's, uh It's kind of the same deal.
所以你就不跟他一起旅行了？
That's why you're not riding with him anymore?
祝我们
Here's to us.
食物可能很糟糕 床可能会很硬
The food might be bad and the beds might be hard…
但是至少我们活在自己的生活中 没有其他人
but at least we're living our own lives…and nobody else's.
不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我们才修了车
We just got the car fixed.
这边
This way.
斯蒂夫
Steve.
谁在那里
Who's there?
回到车上去
Get back to your car.
快走 走啊
Go! Go!
跑啊 跑啊
Run! Run!
这是什么
What?
这到底是什么
What the hell was that?
别问
Don't ask.
稻草人爬下了架子？
The scarecrow climbed off its cross?
我告诉你 伯克斯威尔是个有趣的镇子
I'm telling you. burkitsville, lndiana. Fun town.
它没杀掉那对夫妇吧？
It didn't kill the couple, did it?
没有 没你我处理不好这种事
No. I can cope without you, you know.
肯定有什么赋予它生命
So something must be animating it.
幽灵
A spirit.
不 不仅仅是幽灵
No, it's more than a spirit.
是神 异教邪神
It's a god. A pagan god, anyway.
为什么那样说？
What makes you say that?
猎杀是每年一次
The annual cycle of its killings.
而且受害者总是一男一女
And the victims are always a man and a woman…
就像某种盛大的祭祀
like some kind of fertility rite.
你应该去看看那些当地居民
And you should see the locals.
他们对待那对夫妇的方式
The way they treated this couple.
就像圣诞火鸡一样把他们喂肥
Fattening them up like a Christmas turkey.
最后的晚餐 给那些献祭的受害者
The last meal. Given to sacrificial victims.
我想那些祭品都是献给同一个异教神
Yeah, l'm thinking a ritual sacrifice to appease some pagan god.
所以神就支配了稻草人
So a god possesses the scarecrow.
稻草人拿走了它的祭品
And the scarecrow takes its sacrifice.
第二年农作物就没落叶病 也不会蔓延开
And for another year, the crops won't wilt and disease won't spread.
你知道对付的是什么神？
Know which god you're dealing with?
不 还不知道
Nope, not yet.
你知道它是什么
Figure out what it is.
你就知道该怎么干掉它
You can figure out a way to kill it.
我知道 我已经在去当地社区学院的路上了
I know. I'm actually on my way to a local community college.
我已经给一个教授约好了
I got an appointment with a professor.
因为已经没有忠实的傻瓜伙计 帮我做这些研究了
You know, since I don't have my trusty sidekick geek boy to do all the research.
如果你在暗示需要帮助 你就直说
You know, if you're hinting you need my help, just ask.
我没暗示任何事
I'm not hinting anything.
事实上
Actually…
我想让你知道
I want you to know…
我并不是那么想的
I mean, don't think…
我知道 我也很抱歉
Yeah. l'm sorry too.
萨姆 你是对的
Sam, you were right.
你应该做你自己的事
You gotta do your own thing.
你要为自己而活
You gotta live your own life.
你认真的？
You serious?
你总是能知道自己需要什么
You've always known what you want.
然后就去追逐它
And you go after it.
你勇敢的抵抗爸爸
You stand up to Dad…
我是说你总是这样
and you always have.
该死 我希望我…
Hell, I wish l.
不管怎么说
Anyway…
我很佩服那样的你
l admire that about you.
我为你而感到骄傲 Sam
I'm proud of you, Sammy.
我不知道该说什么了
I don't even know what to say.
说你会照顾好自己
Say you'll take care of yourself.
我会的
I will.
找到爸爸给我打电话
Call me when you find Dad.
好的 再见迪恩
Okay. Bye, Dean.
是谁？
Who was that?
我哥哥
My brother.
他说什么了
What'd he say?
「再见」
Goodbye.
并不是每天都有人来问关于邪神崇拜的研究
It's not every day I get a research question on pagan idolatry.
是的 这只是业余爱好
Yeah, well, call it a hobby.
你说你只是对本地传说感兴趣？
But you said you were interested in local lore?
我想印地安那并是不因为异教崇拜而出名吧
I'm afraid Indiana isn't really known for its pagan worship.
如果它是外来的呢
What if it was imported?
就像一些流浪者把他们的信仰到处传播
Like the Pilgrims brought their religion over.
这里大部分地方不都是由移民开发的吗？
Wasn't this area settled by immigrants?
就像这附近的小镇伯克斯威尔
Like that town near here, Burkitsville.
他们的祖先来自什么地方？
Where are their ancestors from?
我想是北欧 斯堪的纳维亚
Northern Europe, I believe. Scandinavia.
那你给我说说那些异教神
What could you tell me about those pagan gods?
斯堪的纳维亚有几百个神和女神
Well, there are hundreds of Norse gods and goddesses.
事实上我只在找一个 可能就住在果园
I'm actually looking for one. Might live in an orchard.
森林之神
A woods god.
好吧 来看看
Well, let's see.
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
这个是什么
What's that one?
这个本质上可不是森林之神
That's not a woods god, per se.
莞讷神？（北欧神话中的神族）
The Vanir?
莞讷神是北欧的保护和繁荣之神
"The Vanir were Norse gods of protection and prosperity…
「保护当地安全免受伤害」
keeping the local settlements safe from harm.
「村民在地里建造莞讷神的雕像」
The villages built effigies of the Vanir in their fields.
「其他村民寻找活人祭品」
Other villages practiced human sacrifice."
「一名男性和一名女性」
"One male and one female"
这看起来像是稻草人
Kind of looks like a scarecrow, huh?
是的 可能吧
Well, I suppose.
「这种特别的莞讷神的能量来源于神木」
This particular Vanir, its energy sprung from a sacred tree?
异教徒认为所有的东西都被注入了魔法
Well, pagans believed all sorts of things were infused with magic.
如果神木被烧掉会怎么样？
So what would happen if the sacred tree was torched?
你认为这会杀了神吗？
You think it'd kill the god?
孩子 我们只是在讨论传说
Son…these are just legends we're discussing here.
那是当然
Oh, of course.
你是对的
Yeah, you're right.
十分感谢
Listen, thank you very much.
很荣幸帮到你
Glad I could help. All right.
你一定得明白 Hurley
You do understand, Harley?
这里的每个人都有责任保护镇子
All of us here, it's It's our responsibility to protect the town.
我明白
I understand.
比你们都明白
Better than all of you.
就是我给他们指路的
I'm the one that gives them directions.
就是我把他们送到果园的
I'm the one that sends them down to the orchard.
赫尔利 拜托
Harley, please.
我们都关上了门
We all close our doors…
把头撇向一边 让我们听不到尖叫
look the other way…pretend we can't hear the screams.
但这次不同
But this is different.
这次是谋杀
This is murder.
它对我们发怒了
It's angry with us.
树已经开始死亡
Already the trees are beginning to die.
今晚是第七个晚上了 我们最后的机会
Tonight's the seventh night of the cycle. Our last chance.
如果那孩子该死 那就让他死
If the boy has to die, the boy has to die.
但为什么要这样对她？
But why does it have to be her?
斯泰西姑妈
Aunt Stacey.
赫尔利伯父 求求你们
Uncle Harley, please.
你们为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
为了共有的神
For the common good.
班车来了
Hey. Our bus came in.
你最好上车
You better catch it.
我得走了
l gotta go.
去哪儿
Go where?
伯克斯威尔
Burkitsville.
萨姆 等等
Sam. Wait.
连续三个小时 我都在给我哥哥打电话
I've been calling my brother for the last three hours.
只能收到他的语音邮件
l'm getting his voicemail.
可能他已经关机了
Maybe his phone's turned off.
不 那不是他的作风
No, that's not like him.
梅格 我想他遇上麻烦了
Meg, I think he might be in trouble.
什么麻烦
What kind of trouble?
现在我不能解释
l can't really explain right now.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我可不想你错过班车
I don't want you to miss your bus.
但是我不明白
But I don't understand.
你要回到你哥哥身边？
You're running back to your brother?
就是你尽力要摆脱的人
The guy you ran away from?
为什么 就因为他没接电话？
Why? Because he won't pick up his phone?
萨姆 来吧 跟我一起去加利福尼亚
Sam. Come. With me to California.
我不能 抱歉
I can't. l'm sorry.
为什么不能
Why not?
他是我的家人
He's my family.
我不明白
I don't understand.
他们要杀了我们？
They're gonna kill us?
拿我们当祭品 我也不清楚 我想是很盛大的那种
Sacrifice us. Which is, I don't know, classier, I guess.
你真的一点也不了解 是不是？
You really didn't know anything about this, did you?
了解什么 稻草人之神？
out what? The scarecrow god?
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
你最好开始相信
Well, you better start believing.
因为我需要你的帮助
Because l'm gonna need your help.
好吧
Okay.
我们可以毁掉那个稻草人
Now, we can destroy the scarecrow.
但是我们得先找到那棵树
But we gotta find the tree.
什么树
What tree?
也许你可以帮我找到
Maybe you can help me with that.
肯定足够古老
It would be really old.
而且当地人对它表现出敬意
The locals would treat it with a lot of respect.
因为它是神圣的
You know, like it was sacred.
有一棵苹果树
There was this one apple tree.
是移民们带来的
The immigrants brought it over with them.
他们叫它「初树」
They call it the First Tree.
在果园里吗？
ls it in the orchard?
是的 但是我不知道确切位置
Yeah, but I don't know where.
是时候了
It's time.
你杀了多少人 长官
How many people have you killed, sheriff?
你双手沾满了多少鲜血
How much blood is on your hands?
我们没杀他们
We don't kill them.
但是你却掩盖了真相
No, but you sure cover up after.
你藏了多少辆车 烧掉了多少件衣服
I mean, how many cars have you hidden, clothes have you buried?
赫尔利伯父 求求你
Uncle Harley, please.
我很抱歉 Emily
I am so sorry, Em.
我也希望那不是你
I wish it wasn't you.
尽力理解吧
Try to understand.
这是我们的职责
It's our responsibility.
别无选择
And there's just no other choice.
别无他人 只有你
There's nobody else but you.
我是你的家人
I'm your family.
亲爱的
Sweetheart…
这才是「牺牲」的真谛
that's what sacrifice means.
为了伟大的神而放弃你的最爱
Giving up something you love for the greater good.
镇子需要解救
The town needs to be saved.
牺牲小我而完成大我
The good of the many outweighs the good of the one.
让你的苹果派去见鬼吧
I hope your apple pie is freaking worth it!
你的计划呢？
So, what's the plan?
我在想
I'm working on it.
你根本就没计划 是吗？
You don't have a plan, do you?
我在想
I'm working on it.
你能看到吗？
Can you see?
- 什么 - 它开始动了吗？
- What? - ls he moving yet?
看不到
I can't see.
我的上帝
Oh, my God.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God!
迪恩
Dean?
我收回之前说的话
I take everything back I said.
看到你真是太高兴
I'm so happy to see you.
快点
Come on.
你怎么到这里的
How'd you get here?
我偷了一辆车
I, uh, stole a car.
这才是我兄弟
That's my boy.
盯着那个稻草人
Keep an eye on that scarecrow.
它随时可能复活
He could come alive any minute.
什么稻草人
What scarecrow?
好了 现在是你说的那个神木
All right. Now, this sacred tree you're talking about.
是它的能量之源
It's the source of its power.
找到它然后烧掉
So let's burn it.
早上的时候
In the morning.
在它皮革脸咬到屁股之前 我们得快一点
Let's just shag ass before Leatherface catches up.
这边
This way.
求求你们 让我们走
Please let us go.
会很快结束的 我保证
It'll be over quickly, I promise.
求求你
Please!
艾米丽 你得让他跟你一起
Emily, you have to let him take you.
我们走
Come on, come on. Let's go.
让我来
Let me.
整个镇子都会消逝
You know, the whole town's gonna die.
那是好事
Good.
你认为她没事吗？
Think she's gonna be all right?
我希望是这样
I hope so.
剩下的那些镇民 他们会离开吗？
And the rest of the townspeople, they'll just get away with it?
镇子的将来已经足够做为惩罚了
What will happen to the town will have to be punishment enough.
我可以把你扔在某地吗？
So can I drop you off somewhere?
不能 我想你离不开我
No, I think you're stuck with me.
什么让你改变主意
What made you change your mind?
没有 我还是想找到爸爸
I didn't. I still wanna find Dad.
而且你也是个讨厌鬼
And you're still a pain in the ass.
但是杰西和妈妈
But Jess and Mom…
她们都死了
they're both gone.
鬼才知道爸爸在哪
Dad is God knows where.
你和我
You and me…
都是家里仅存的
we're all that's left.
如果我们能看穿这一切
So, uh, if we're gonna see this through…
就能一起来干
we're gonna do it together.
拥抱一下 萨姆
Hold me, Sam.
说得太好了
That was beautiful. Come on.
行了吧 你应该亲我屁屁表示感谢
You should be kissing my ass.
不然你就死定了 伙计
You were dead meat, dude.
是啊
Yeah, right.
当时我已经有个计划怎么逃脱了
I had a plan. I'd have gotten out.
是啊
Right.
到哪儿 美女
So where to, pretty lady?
把车子开到路边好吗
How about you pull over?
好的
Okay.
照办
That works.
那是什么
What's that?
我要进行通话
I've got to make a call.
你可以用我的手机
l got a cell you can use.
不是你所谓的通话
It's not that kind of call.
谢谢你的顺风车
Thanks for the ride.
[咒语]
[SPEAKING IN LATIN]
这完全没意义
It makes no sense.
我可以阻止Sam
I could have stopped Sam.
该死 我可以把他们都带走
Hell, I could've taken them both.
为什么让他们离开
Why let them go?
是
Yes.
遵命 父亲
Yes, Father.